A full football match contains a few moments people need,
buried inside everything else.
Every Angle finds those moments,
then makes a human the final authority.
The system narrows the footage, Claude proposes what happened,
and an editor reviews the evidence.
Only verified events reach this match summary,
search, or the final reel.
The provenance timeline keeps the whole process visible:
candidate windows below, human decisions alongside them,
and every available verified clip playable in place.
Here is the human-in-the-loop step.
The model suggests a goal from the visual sequence.
The editor can inspect the footage, correct the description,
reject it, or keep it.
This decision updates the verified manifest.
Search is grounded in that manifest,
not raw model output.
A natural-language query finds the verified moment where the keeper
comes off his line, with its clip and provenance attached.
Quick Highlights groups replay-adjacent incidents
and selects a deterministic edit.
The organizer can change the order, while FFmpeg assembles the reel
without another model call.
For a club or content team, that turns a long recording into searchable,
ready-to-share moments — while keeping the person, the evidence, and the rights boundary in control.
Every Angle.
Find the moments.
Prove every one.